{
    "subject": "resource/Augusto_Lauro",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Tarvisio",
    "human_readable": "Augusto Lauro was born in Tarvisio.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8875089883804321,
            "question": "Where was Augusto Lauro born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8230450749397278,
            "question": "What year was Augusto Lauro born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7889098525047302,
            "question": "Was Augusto Lauro born in a city or a rural area?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4352743923664093,
            "question": "Is Augusto Lauro known for anything specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4042453169822693,
            "question": "Do you know any other facts about Augusto Lauro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3732667863368988,
            "question": "What country is Tarvisio located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28138357400894165,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the history of Tarvisio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23547260463237762,
            "question": "Is Tarvisio a popular tourist destination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21180978417396545,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks or attractions in Tarvisio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19232302904129028,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Tarvisio?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Augusto Lauro was born in Tarvisio.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2823_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous landmarks or attractions in Tarvisio?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2823_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Tarvisio a popular tourist destination?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2823_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the history of Tarvisio?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2823_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2823_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2823_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2823_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2823_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2823_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2823_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2823_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2823_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2823_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2823_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe document states that \"Lauro was born in Tarvisio,\" which supports the statement that Augusto Lauro was born in Tarvisio."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}